A Guide to the Virginia Dietetic Association Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 10, No. 2), April, 1950, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 10, No. 3), July, 1950, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 11, No. 1), November, 1950, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 11, No. 2), March, 1951, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 11, No. 3), August, 1951, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 12, No. 1), January, 1952, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 12, No. 2), June, 1952, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 12, No. 3), December, 1952, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 13, No. 1), April, 1953, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 13, No. 2), August, 1953, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 13, No. 3), November, 1953, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 14, No. 3), October, 1954, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:025)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 15, No. 2), September, 1955, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 15, No. 3), January, 1956, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 16, No. 2), November, 1956, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 17, No. 1), February, 1957, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 18, No. 1), February, 1958, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:030)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 18, No. 2), August, 1958, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:031)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 19, No. 1), February, 1992, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:032)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 19, No. 2), June, 1959, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:033)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 19, No. 3), November, 1959, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 037:034)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 20, No. 1), February, 1960, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 21, No. 2), August, 1961, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 21, No. 3), December, 1961, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 22, No. 1), Spring, 1962, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 22, No. 2), Summer, 1962, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 22, No. 3), Fall, 1962, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 23, No. 1), Spring, 1963, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 23, No. 2), Summer, 1963, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 23, No. 3), Fall, 1963, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 24, No. 2), Spring, 1964, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 24, No. 2), Summer, 1964, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 24, No. 3), Fall, 1964, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 25, No. 1), Spring, 1965, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 25, No. 2), Summer, 1965, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 25, No. 3), Winter, 1965-1966, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 26, No. 1), Spring, 1966, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 26, No. 2), Summer, 1966, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 26, No. 3), Fall, 1966, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 27, No. 1), Spring, 1967, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 27, No. 2), Summer, 1967, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 27, No. 3), Fall, 1967, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 28, No. 1), Spring, 1968, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 28, No. 2), Summer, 1968, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 28, No. 3), Fall, 1968, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 29, No. 1), Spring, 1969, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:025)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 29, No. 2), Summer, 1969, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 29, No. 3), Fall, 1969, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 038:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 30, No. 1), Summer 1970, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 30, No. 1), Summer, 1971, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 30, No. 1), Spring, 1970, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 30, No. 2), Fall, 1970, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 31, No. 2), Spring, 1971, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, Fall, 1971, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, winter, 1971, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, November, 1971, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, March, 1972, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, Fall, 1973, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, Spring, 1974, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, October, 1974, Newsletter() (Box-folder 039:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, Winter, 1974, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, March, 1975, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, July, 1975, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, May, 1976, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, January, 1978, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, June, 1978, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, October, 1978, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, March, 1979, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 1, No. 2), June, 1979, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 1, No. 3), October, 1979, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 2, No. 1), January, 1980, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 2, No. 4), November, 1980, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 3, No. 3), May, 1983, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:025)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 4, No. 1), May, 1984, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 4, No. 2), December, 1984, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines Newsletter, Winter/Spring, 1984, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 5, No. 1), May, 1985, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 5, No. 2), December, 1985, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:030)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 6, No. 1), May, 1986, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:031)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 6, No. 2), December, 1986, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:032)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 7, No. 1), June, 1987, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:033)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines (Vol. 7, No. 3), December, 1987, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:034)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines, January, 1989, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:035)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines, June, 1989, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:036)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines, January, 1990, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:037)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VaDA Lines, March, 1992, Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 039:038)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, October, 1981, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 040:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, October, 1982, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 040:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, October, 1983, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 040:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, October, 1984, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 040:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, October, 1985, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 040:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, December, 1985, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 040:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, December, 1986, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 040:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, 1987-1988, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 041:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, 1988-1989, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 041:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, 1989-1990, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 041:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, 1990-1991, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 041:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, 1991-1992, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 041:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, 1993-1994, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 041:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, 1994-1995, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 041:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Financial Statements, 1995-1996, Booklet(1) (Box-folder 041:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Treasurer's Handbook, 1987, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 042:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Treasurer's Handbook, 1988, Manual Book(1) (Box-folder 042:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1982, Disbursement Request Forms(11) (Box-folder 043:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1983, Disbursement Request Forms(102) (Box-folder 043:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1984, Disbursement Request Forms(178) (Box-folder 043:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1985, Disbursement Request Forms(31) (Box-folder 043:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1986, Disbursement Request Forms(201) (Box-folder 043:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1987, Disbursement Request Forms(158) (Box-folder 044:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1988, Disbursement Request Forms(148) (Box-folder 044:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1989, Disbursement Request Forms(173) (Box-folder 044:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1990, Disbursement Request Forms(80) (Box-folder 044:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1991, Disbursement Request Forms(13) (Box-folder 044:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1992, Disbursement Request Forms(183) (Box-folder 044:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1993, Disbursement Request Forms(23) (Box-folder 044:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Disbursement Requests, 1994, Disbursement Request Forms(47) (Box-folder 044:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Application for Continuing Education(1), 1983, Request Forms (Box-folder 045:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Application for Continuing Education(2), 1984, Request Forms (Box-folder 045:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Application for Continuing Education(1), 1985, Request Forms (Box-folder 046:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Application for Continuing Education(2), 1985, Request Forms (Box-folder 046:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Scholarship Award Committee Reports, 1956-1992, TD(69) (Box-folder 047:001)
  Reports, Letters, Scholarship Application Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Recipients, 1963-1992, TD(6) (Box-folder 047:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Recipients, 1988-1989, TD(2) (Box-folder 047:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Application and Recipients, 1990, TD(9) (Box-folder 047:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Application and Recipients, 1991, TD(6), AD(6) (Box-folder 047:005)
  Letters, News Releases, Card
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Application and Recipients, 1992, TD(23), AD(1), Namecard(1) (Box-folder 047:006)
  Letters, Graduate Scholarship Application Forms, Student Grade Report, Personal Statements
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Dietetic Technician Scholarship Application, 1993, TD(16), AD(2) (Box-folder 047:007)
  Letters, Graduate Scholarship Application Forms, Student Grade Reports, Personal Statements
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Margaret McDonald Memorial Scholarship Application, 1993, TD(48) (Box-folder 047:008)
  Resumes, Letters, Student Grade Reports, Personal Statements
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Joan Dobek Harrell-Ross Professional Development Award Application, 1993, TD(26) (Box-folder 047:009)
  Resumes, Letters, Award Application Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Graduate Scholarship Application, 1993, TD(16) (Box-folder 047:011)
  Resumes, Letters, Scholarship Application Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Recipients, 1993, TD(26), AD(1), Newsletter(1), Disbursement Request Form(1) (Box-folder 047:012)
  Letters, News Releases, Card, Memoranda
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Dietetic Technician Scholarship Application, 1994, TD(17) (Box-folder 047:013)
  Letters, Scholarship Application Forms, Student Grade Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Margaret McDonald Memorial Scholarship Applications, 1994, TD(23) (Box-folder 047:014)
  Letters, Scholarship Application Forms, Resumes, Student Grade Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Graduate Scholarship Application, 1994, TD(36) (Box-folder 047:015)
  Letters, Scholarship Application Forms, Resumes
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Joan Dobek Harrell-Ross Professional Development Award Application, 1994, TD(65) (Box-folder 047:016)
  Letters, Award Application Forms, Resumes
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Recipients, 1994, TD(25), AD(2) (Box-folder 047:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Dietetic Technician Scholarship Application, 1995, TD(24), AD(3) (Box-folder 047:018)
  Scholarship Application Forms, Student Grade Reports, Personal Statements, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Margaret McDonald Memorial Scholarship Application, 1995, TD(17) (Box-folder 047:019)
  Program Application Forms, Student Grade Reports, Letters, CV
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Graduate Scholarship Application, 1995, TD(15) (Box-folder 047:020)
  Scholarship Application Forms, Letters, CV
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Joan Dobek Harrell-Ross Professional Development Award Application, 1995, TD(9) (Box-folder 047:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Recipients, 1995, TD(17), AD(2) (Box-folder 047:022)
  Memorandum, Applicants Rating Sheets, Reports, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Graduate Scholarship Application, 1996, TD(59) (Box-folder 048:001)
  Resumes, Letters, Scholarship Application Forms, Student Grade Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Margaret McDonald Memorial Scholarship, 1996, TD(28) (Box-folder 048:002)
  Letters, Resumes, Student Grade Reports, Program Application Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Joan Dobek Harrell-Ross Professional Development Award Application, 1996, TD(11) (Box-folder 048:003)
  Application Forms, CV, Letters, Information on the 36th Annual Meeting
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Recipients 1996, TD(18), AD(2) (Box-folder 048:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Dietetic Technician Scholarship Application, 1997, TD(9) (Box-folder 048:005)
  Scholarship Application Forms, Letters, Student Grade Report
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Joan Dobek Harrell-Ross Professional Development Award Application, 1997, TD(17), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 048:006)
  Award Application Form, Letters, Resume
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Margaret McDonald Memorial Scholarship Application, 1997, TD(44) (Box-folder 048:007)
  Program Application Form, Letters, Student Grade Reports, Personal Statements
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Recipients, 1997, TD(11) (Box-folder 048:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Dietetic Technician Scholarship Application, 1998, TD(7) (Box-folder 048:009)
  Scholarship Application Forms, Reports, Letters, Grade Reports,
- Virginia Dietetic Association: VDA Professional Development Award Application, 1998, TD(10) (Box-folder 048:010)
  Memorandum, Report, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Graduate Scholarship Application, 1998, TD(12) (Box-folder 048:011)
  Letters, Scholarship Application Form,
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Margaret McDonald Memorial Scholarship Application, 1998, TD(17) (Box-folder 048:012)
  Reports, Memorandum, Letters, Student Grade Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Award Recipients, 1998, TD(13), AD(1), Photo(1) (Box-folder 048:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Margaret McDonald Memorial Scholarship Application, 1999, TD(14) (Box-folder 048:014)
  Scholarship Application Forms, Letters, Student Report Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Reports on John G. Kolbe Award, 1954-1976, TD(72), Newspaper Clippings(3) (Box-folder 049:001)
  Nomination Forms, Reports, Letters, News Releases
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1955, TD(3) (Box-folder 049:002)
  News Release
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1956, TD(11), Newspaper Article(1), Photo(1) (Box-folder 049:003)
  Nomination Forms, News Releases
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1957, TD(3) (Box-folder 049:004)
  News Releases
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1958, TD(3) (Box-folder 049:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1959, TD(6) (Box-folder 049:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1960, TD(3) (Box-folder 049:007)
  Nomination Forms, Letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1961, TD(5) (Box-folder 049:008)
  Letter, News Release
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1962, TD(8) (Box-folder 049:009)
  Nomination Forms, Reports, Letters, News Release
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1963, TD(24) (Box-folder 049:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1964, TD(11) (Box-folder 049:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1965, TD(19), Newspaper Clippings(2) (Box-folder 049:012)
  Nomination Forms, Reports, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1966, TD(17), AD(2) (Box-folder 049:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1967, TD(14) (Box-folder 049:014)
  Nomination Forms, Letters, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1968, TD(19), AD(1), Newspaper Clipping(1) (Box-folder 049:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1969, TD(27) (Box-folder 049:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1970, TD(6), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 049:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: John G. Kolbe Award Recipient, 1971, TD(4) (Box-folder 049:018)
  Nomination Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Minute Book, 1929-1934, Minute Book(1) (Box-folder 050:001)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Semi-Annual Meeting, November 9-10, 1934, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:002)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Seventh Annual Convention, April 12-13, 1935, Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 050:003)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Semi-Annual Meeting, November 15-16, 1935, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:004)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Annual Convention, April 15-18, 1936, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:005)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Annual Convention, April 16-17, 1937, TD(1) (Box-folder 050:006)
  Meeting Report
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Joint Meeting of the Virginia Home Economics Association and the Virginia State Dietetic Association, March 25-26, 1938, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:007)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Ninth Annual Convention - Carolinas-Virginia Hospital Conference, April 20-22, 1939, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:008)
- Virginia State Dietetic Association: Dinner Meeting - "War Time Nutrition in England", March 26, 1943, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Meeting, May 11, 1945, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: State Meeting, November 9-10, 1945, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meetings, 1945, TD(4) (Box-folder 050:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Meetings, 1945, TD(4) (Box-folder 050:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meeting, 1946, TD(1) (Box-folder 050:014)
  Minute
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meetings, 1946, TD(8) (Box-folder 050:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Fall Meeting, November 15-16, 1946, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meetings, 1947, TD(3) (Box-folder 050:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Board Meetings, 1947, TD(6) (Box-folder 050:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Seventh Annual Convention of Carolinas-Virginia Hospital Conference, April 2-4, 1947, Pamphlets(3) (Box-folder 050:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Meetings, 1948, TD(11) (Box-folder 050:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1948, TD(6) (Box-folder 050:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Regular Business Meetings, 1949, TD(8), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1949, TD(7) (Box-folder 050:023)
- Virginia Home Economics Dietetic Associations: Joint Meeting, April 1-3, 1949, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Regular Business Meetings, 1950, TD(5), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 050:025)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1950, TD(8), AD(1) (Box-folder 050:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meetings, 1951, TD(4), Pamphlet(2) (Box-folder 050:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Executive Committee Meetings, 1951, TD(5) (Box-folder 050:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: Business Meetings, 1952, TD(4), Pamphlet(2) (Box-folder 050:029)